mogicons.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy Policy

## Website Privacy

### Data Collection

We do _not_ collect any personal data.

We use _Google Analytics_ to track and examine the use of _www.mogicons.com_ to prepare reports on its activities. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Find Google's [privacy policy here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). 

### Cookies

Our advertising partners include Google Adsense which may employ cookies on our site. Google uses cookies to serve ads. You may wish to visit Google Adsense for additional information about their privacy policies as well.

### Children Under 13 Years of Age

Note that we do not collect any personal data at all.

### External Links

Our website may contain links to third-party websites. These third party websites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information.

### Information Sharing

_www.mogicons.com_ has no personal information to share.

## Add-on "Facebook Secret Emoticons" Privacy

### Data Collection

We do _not_ collect or use any data from your Facebook account! 

### Cookies

We don't use cookies.

### External Links

Our Add-on contains links to our website [www.mogicons.com](http://www.mogicons.com/ "Facebook Smileys")

### Children Under 13 Years of Age

Note that we do not collect any personal data at all.

### Information Sharing

We don't have any personal information to share.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change our policy at any time by posting a new version of it on the Website. If you object to the change to our Privacy Policy, then you must contact us in writing regarding your objection.

### Question and Comments

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [admin@mogicons.com](mailto:admin@mogicons.com)
